{
    "subject": "resource/H._H._Asquith",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Morley,_West_Yorkshire",
    "human_readable": "H.H. Asquith was born in Morley, West Yorkshire.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9842645525932312,
            "question": "Were there any notable people born in Morley, West Yorkshire besides H.H. Asquith?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.921085774898529,
            "question": "Where was H.H. Asquith born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8516116142272949,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where H.H. Asquith was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8316217660903931,
            "question": "In which county was H.H. Asquith born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.580001175403595,
            "question": "What is the significance of Morley, West Yorkshire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5627691149711609,
            "question": "What is the history of Morley, West Yorkshire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5474528670310974,
            "question": "Was H.H. Asquith a public figure?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5143070816993713,
            "question": "What time period was H.H. Asquith associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49321889877319336,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about H.H. Asquith?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3353016674518585,
            "question": "Is there any connection between H.H. Asquith and British politics?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=H.H. Asquith was born in Morley, West Yorkshire.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3135_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about H.H. Asquith?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3135_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What time period was H.H. Asquith associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3135_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was H.H. Asquith a public figure?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3135_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3135_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3135_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3135_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3135_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3135_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3135_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3135_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3135_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3135_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3135_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents consistently mention that Herbert Henry Asquith (referred to as H.H. Asquith) was born in Morley, which is located in West Yorkshire, England."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}